JESSE BETT

Software Developer | +254798790147

O DETAILS O 0798790147

jessekip21@gmail.com

o SKILLS o

JavaScript

NodeJs

ExpressJs

JWT Auth

Python

Mongo

SQL

NestJs

Version control

o HOBBIES c

Football

Chess

O Links O

https://github.com/Jesse-Bett

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jesse-bett-74b3411a7

my portfolio - jessebett.herokuapp.com

PROFILE

I'm a software developer whose primary goal is to apply technical expertise all throughout the full software life cycle to ensure the production and delivery of world-class products and services that meet client specifications. Along with a competent software development team, and with strong personal knowledge, skills, and experience in software engineering. I'm passionate about solving problems, understanding how things work and how I could improve them.

EDUCATION

Kabarak University Nakuru, Kenya

2018 - 2021

BSc. Information Technology

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

JamboPay

May 2022 - Current

Duties/Responsibilities.

- Performing web integrations between customer website and Jam boPay checkout.
- Developing and maintaining our email and SMS systems.
- Developing e-commerce web apps to assist in testing integration plugins and writing API documentation.
- Monitoring Jambopay systems to detect and resolve downtime.
- Supporting internal staff in network, hardware, and software issues.

NHIF - Internship

Septemeber 2021 - December 2021

Duties/Responsibilities.

- Network connectivity of client computers both to the Local AreaNetwork and the Internet.
- Configuration of new PCs and Servers on an acquisition.
- Performing updates on current system requirements for the institution.
- Setting up of ad-hoc networks during conferences and Multimedia set up and support.
- Hardware repairs, maintenance and peripheral devices installation.
- Data recovery, User assistance, User Support.